[♪ epic theme music playing]
[wind lightly whooshing]
[♪ soft. dramatic music playing]
[horse nickering]
[heavy doors open]
[Rhaenyra] [echoing voice]
Helaena.
[voice clear]
[gasps lightly]
I'm sorry to disturb
your rest.
Have you heard w-word
from my mother?
No.
Nor do I expect to. until...
[birdsong]
Did Aemond ask you
to ride into battle with him?
Hm.
Lord Corlys
imagined he would.
When I was a girl.
I wanted to fly.
But now. when...
when I'm with Dreamfyre...
it's...
and then too much.
I think our father
felt the same way.
He renounced
the strength of dragons
and embraced a quieter life.
He did not wish
to be changed.
You believe the dragons
alter us in some way?
You now have many dragons.
Are you yourself not altered?
[scoffs] No.
Well. I do not wish to be.
I wished only
to put an end to our contest
and restore us
to our proper order.
[sighs]
Helaena.
Sister. I believe that you...
may be a dreamer.
That you...
see things.
I see f-flashes sometimes.
Some cl-clearer
than others.
What did you see last?
A gray mare.
Mm-hmm.
What of Daemon?
Have you seen him?
Hm?
The Winter Wolves. then.
Or Tumbleton.
Will Ormund Hightower
be brought to heel?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Or you will not say?
You may refuse me
as your sister.
but I may compel you
as your queen.
Now. tell me what you know!
Tell me there has been
no mistake.
that I will prevail.
as the gods must surely intend.
Tell me.
♪
[grunting]
[groaning]
Mother.
I told you I would come.
if I could.
Were you not taken captive?
Your sister was taken.
But I managed
to stay hidden. to escape.
You have been so clever
to remain here undiscovered.
I thought all had
forsaken me.
[sighs]
How could I forsake...
my best...
and truest son?
The city has fallen. Aemond.
- [soft kiss]
- You're all I have left.
[Alicent sighs]
The road has been long
and perilous.
so I'll be glad of a bed.
What of Aegon?
Aegon is most likely dead.
I did all I could.
And for you.
[whispering]
But I have failed you. Aemond.
No.
- I was too young.
- Never.
I was just a child.
[sighs. sniffles]
[Alicent moaning]
And in this moment
I will give you a son.
[Aemond moaning]
Aemond.
- What have you seen?
- [gasps] Please.
[creatures chittering]
[footsteps approaching]
Aemond.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Gwayne] Open the gates!
[people chattering]
[chattering continues]
They've crossed
the Blackwater Rush.
- How many?
- Twenty thousand.
A day's march away.
Two at most.
So. your dim
but ambitious Dornish friend
died in the mud for nothing.
That is no matter.
I have a piece
on the board now
that will bring the bitch
to her knees.
And what is that?
[sighs]
[Caraxes bellowing]
[whistling]
[chittering]
- My prince...
- Move!
Where is she?
Where's Rhaena?
I see we are dispensing
with courtesies.
Is she here?
She flew. just after
I sent to you.
I could not hold her.
Put her in chains
if you have to. lock her in a cell.
Do you imagine it's so easy
to force a dragonrider
to do what she does not wish?
She exposes me. too.
She beseeched me
with tears in her eyes.
swore that she would
remain here in hiding.
Talk of a dragonrider
is rife in the Vale.
The villagers gossip
of a wild girl in the mountains
living amongst
nettles and sheep.
I am finished
with the matter.
It is in my best interest now
to alert the queen
- to her flight.
- No.
You may blunt
Rhaenyra's wrath.
but you will not evade it.
Give me a day.
Please.
She has been here and there
seeking news of Vhagar.
There's word of a sighting
near Fairmarket.
so I can only assume...
[dragon vocalizing]
[Baela] We are two days
behind Aemond at best.
I have long tired
of this endless searching.
I cannot help but think
I'm being punished by Rhaenyra.
or at least sent far
from her sight.
She thinks of us
only as tools to be wielded.
I wondered. my lady.
if I might beg you for a kindness.
My father wishes for Alyn
and me to be legitimized
and take the Velaryon name.
The queen
is being reluctant.
You know my standing
after the Gullet.
I do not think my words
would have much sway with her.
But your father. perhaps.
Why this concern now
with names and titles?
- [dragon screeching]
- I understand your grievance.
but surely. you have
a better thing in your dragon
than any lordly appellation.
It is only that
if either of us were to marry.
That is...
if either of us gained the favor
of some highborn lady.
[scoffs]
He has spoken to you. then.
Your brother.
[dragons bellowing]
Is it Vhagar?
No.
I did not think us like
to escape the Red Keep.
But Ser Adrian remained
steadfast and resolute.
He led us
to a secret gate. and...
and I had enough coin
with me for horses.
We tried to remain
off the roads.
but the forests have become
impassable in places.
There are wild men
in the woods now.
I would not have arrived here
if it wasn't for him.
Rhaenyra took the castle.
but he remained loyal.
He helped me at great risk
to his own person.
He is a gr... [gasps]
Have I offended you?
No.
You are all I have left.
- [footsteps receding]
- [sighs]
[footsteps approaching]
This is he.
my protector and guide.
Ser Adrian.
Your Grace.
Mm.
[sighs]
Well. it seems
I owe you a debt.
I did only
as my conscience demanded.
The queen dowager
was treated shamefully.
- [blade thwacking]
- [Alicent] Aemond!
[gurgling]
[body thuds]
Sorry. Mother.
There are secrets here.
and I can trust no stranger.
[Alys] Ah. there you are.
You're just in time
for supper.
[liquid pouring]
The maesters tell me
the fat of livestock
is beneficial to the bones.
But I do wonder how something
so slippery in substance
can truly be benign.
[chuckles]
Do try the wine. Lord Corlys.
I find it wards off
the fetid air of this place.
Mm.
What are you about.
Hightower?
Is this some kind
of final repast?
Pigeon pie before
the executioner's block?
On the contrary.
We hope to enjoy
the pleasure of your company
for quite some time.
You will be of great assistance
to us in our little endeavor.
- As what? A hostage?
- Hm.
Does the savage queen
harbor such a tender heart
that she should
cast away her crown
for the sake of her
wayward Hand?
I think not.
The Velaryons. however.
with their lord as forfeit.
the men of Driftmark
will think better
of entering King's Landing.
And without them. the city will again
eat of its own disorder.
H-How will that help
when the Winter Wolves
are clawing at our gates?
Do you know?
More and more I am inclined
to limit my diet...
to the vegetable kingdom.
Just as the people of Naathi do.
If you have finished
with your instruction...
What do you see in them. anyway?
The Targaryen...
element.
You are a traveled man.
you have seen
the world's wonders.
Why limit yourself
in tedious alliance
to the brutish
and the incurious?
Your wife. of course.
was of their blood.
That ended all too predictably.
I would think.
after having seen
how they devour
one of their own...
I would like to return
to my cell.
As you please.
Oh. Lord Corlys?
Before you go...
He was in uncommon
good spirits...
as though he were on the eve
of some great victory.
He seems to believe that
with Lord Corlys as hos...
Is this his
"piece on the board"?
What does the order or disorder
of King's Landing
matter to us now
with an army at the gates?
I'm supposed to be the king.
What sort of ruler am I?
Am I to sit by impotent
while a madman
offers us up
for the slaughter?
And all of our men with us?
Seems there's no escaping it.
The dream some have of covering themselves
in everlasting glory...
of somehow transcending
humanity's common fate.
I am sorry about your friend.
[sniffling]
He gave himself to the dust.
I could order the army
to surrender.
[scoffs]
And then what?
Have us all marched
to the gallows?
You could fly away
on Tessarion.
Without you
as a pretext for...
He would continue
as he began.
Where would I go?
Who would receive a king who
left his own men to their ruin?
I have no fear
of insignificance. Gwayne.
Rhaenyra may keep her crown.
for all I care.
[chuckles softly]
[Torrhen Manderly]
Frankly. it is outrageous.
There is a campaign against me!
Jeering in the streets.
My own daughter found
the doorstep of my city dwelling
smeared with some sort of
foul matter.
I don't know what you
want me to do about it.
My queen.
With respect.
In front of petitioners.
you named me responsible
for the current financial
grievances in the city.
I hardly be...
Well. what have you done
to alleviate them?
What can I do?
I have advocated for a tax.
It has fallen on deaf ears.
Our dribbles of gold are spent
as fast as they are gathered.
It's as if I have been
installed here
as some sort of scapegoat.
Has there been any word
from Lord Corlys?
From Harrenhal?
- And Daemon?
- [Orwyle] Absent.
The prince is on some...
errand of his own.
The Keepers say he flew out
of the city before dawn.
The river host
are but a day's march
from Tumbleton. Your Grace.
and the Velaryon forces will be
at King's Landing on the morrow.
I have a reputation
to uphold.
If Ser Adrian
has been successful
in his endeavor. of course.
then there is the small matter
of Harrenhal...
Just take it.
Your Grace?
Return to the Twins
and lead the men you have
left there to Harrenhal.
[gasps]
This I will do gladly!
If Aemond is dead.
all the better.
But in any case. you shall occupy it again.
and leave no place
- for him to return.
- [door opens]
- [Addam] My queen.
- [footsteps approaching]
We have seen
something strange.
- Vhagar?
- No.
Sheepstealer.
In the Riverlands.
on the banks of the Blue Fork
near Fairmarket.
That is unexpected.
He's not known...
Your Grace. he has a rider.
- A new rider?
- I could not say.
We gave chase.
but lost him in the hills.
[high-pitch ringing.
sounds muffling]
That head
Daemon brought to you.
can you say in honesty
you've had no doubts?
He was long in the Riverlands.
and now Sheepstealer
is sighted there with a rider
he assured you was dead.
And in that same moment.
he has absented himself
without explanation.
I have known him to lie.
but this is a great...
You and I have known him to be
capable of far worse than lies.
He has chafed
since you arrived here
over your restraint
in wielding power.
He is impetuous
and impatient.
Who can say what alliance
he may have formed in secret
- when he found you lacking.
- He has sworn to serve me.
I cannot believe that now.
when I need him most.
- that he would...
- Forgive me.
Your Grace.
But is there anything
Daemon could do
that you would truly
not believe?
Fetch Ser Addam.
They say it is the strength
of the sun in Volantis
that makes for such sweetness
in the grape.
If you mean to console me
for this folly
with Volantene wines.
you're much mistaken.
Your Grace.
I beg you. reconsider.
At Maidenpool. we might take ship
for Casterly Rock instead.
[Aegon]
No. I am decided on Braavos.
How much further
must we ride?
Some days still to the port.
Braavos will prove itself
a most cultivated city.
- I assure you.
- [pig squealing]
Perhaps even
a home from home.
[pig squealing]
Whoa.
My good woman.
what is it you flee?
An army marches this way.
- Some thousand strong.
- Which army?
My daughter said she saw
the red fish on the white.
- The Mootons.
- That's where we are going. to Maidenpool.
We must keep moving.
Turn back if you can.
Mootons are sworn to Rhaenyra.
They can't have
heard about me?
Hyah.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[distant people chattering]
[Tyland]
The road is lost to us.
We must fall back
to Rook's Rest.
We can't go back there.
We may have been discovered.
There is an army coming for us
and we have no place to shelter.
There are thick walls
at Rook's Rest
and enough men
to defend them.
It shall be refuge for His Grace
till Mooton's host has passed.
[utensils clacking]
- [Aemond] Mm.
- [Alys] You must be famished.
It's a long journey
from King's Landing.
Yes.
And fraught. no doubt.
If half the tales I have heard
about the King's Road are true.
How is it that the two of you
- came to know one another?
- Mm.
She saved my life.
At whose behest?
Your lord's?
I generally follow
my own dictates.
[laughing] Aemond. I still don't
understand who this woman is.
[sighs]
Mm.
She is a lady.
And a maester. of sorts.
The care of the castle
has fallen to her for now.
I've decided
to stay here with her
and make this place my seat.
Your seat?
Was that not what you
yourself suggested?
A new fortress
from which to rule.
Rhaenyra has the throne
and six dragons to her name.
It is she who rules now. as much as we
might wish it otherwise.
Mm.
Rhaenyra's dragons
are ridden by commoners.
She's defiled our great house.
diminished the Iron Throne.
and sowed the seeds
of her own ruin.
She will certainly fail.
And we will raise
our own throne.
In the mud of the Riverlands.
A new dawn is coming.
A new line of unsullied kings.
We need only to bide our time.
And you. Mother.
You will wait with us.
You have worth yet to offer.
I'm sure your mother
will wish to move on.
Back to Oldtown. perhaps.
Our climate
doesn't seem to suit her.
Mm. there's nothing for her there.
I am all she has left.
- [Alicent] There is Helaena.
- No!
You'll stay with us.
We're out of wood.
[plate clattering]
I will not be coddled or admonished
like a witless child.
Tread carefully
with her. Aemond.
She's come to do you some ill.
She is my blood.
- [wood chopping]
- And thus without blemish?
She's always had her secrets.
most of them poorly kept.
My designs for our future
did not include your mother.
And there is the truth of it.
You want me for yourself.
There is a fog
that surrounds her.
She has come
to do you some evil.
You would be wise to keep
your dark thoughts to yourself.
You Targaryen boys all want
the same thing. don't you?
[panting]
[sniffling]
[breathing heavily]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
- [panicked chatter]
- [baby crying]
Tom Tangletongue. what news?
Lord Mooton of Maidenpool.
he's dispatched an army.
They're marching in haste.
Have you not seen our Janos?
I thought he'd be with you.
No. Where are they marching?
They were commanded here.
to Rook's Rest.
But they're going
village to village. it seems.
in search
of your friend Lannister.
Something about
the queen's gold.
They'll be here before w-we know it.
You'd best be on the move.
[groaning]
[grunting]
I think you'll agree.
Ser Tyland.
that you should
give yourself up.
She will flay me alive.
No doubt.
But once Mooton has you in hand.
he'll turn towards King's Landing.
and His Grace and I
- may yet slip away.
- Give the king to me and my men.
We will ride hard
and escape Mooton's clutches.
Oh. must you be so thick?
Rhaenyra is hunting you.
His Grace is not safe
in your company.
Turn yourself in
and give him the chance to flee.
[Tyland] Him or you?
[Larys]
It is the honorable thing to do.
- Your Grace. for now. at least...
- No.
No.
Go where you will.
Both of you.
Preserve your own skins.
But I shall run no more.
If you do not run.
Your Grace. you will die.
Then I'll die.
But not as a fugitive.
Unknown.
Covered in dust.
Not with an arrow in my back
or trapped like a fox in a hole.
This... this is absurd.
Ser Tyland. I entreat you
- to reason with His Grace.
- I'll make my stand here.
Mm.
And be buried as a king.
With my dragon.
I will not have the histories
say that I was slain
in ignominy
by my own brother.
If the king wishes
to remain. then...
I shall remain with him.
I cannot leave him to face
an army meant for me.
[horses neighing]
You're resolved in this then?
Well then. my lords...
it seems there is only one thing
left for me to do.
May the Seven
be ever at your side.
[Tyland]
You would abandon your master?
I am a cripple. Ser Tyland.
Humble enough to admit
that my presence in a fight
would make
no earthly difference.
Of course. if my king
commanded me to stay...
What Lord Larys says is true.
He would be no use to us here.
Well. then.
It will be my duty to see
that King Aegon is remembered.
His heroic last hours
immortalized through story...
- [chuckles softly]
- ...and song.
Your Grace.
[sighs]
Come. come. come.
[Sheepstealer bellowing]
[screeching]
[Caraxes whistling]
[chittering]
[bellowing]
[dragons screeching.
bellowing]
- Stay back!
- You swore to me.
- You should not have come.
- Did you think she would not hear of this?
Stay back!
He does not heed me!
[roaring]
Daor!
[screeching]
What do you hope to do here?
In the reeds and the mud?
Vhagar was here.
Or near here. last I heard.
We heard the same.
but she is gone.
Then I will fly
in search of her.
And if you find her?
I thought I could do this.
but I can't.
I cannot live the way I have.
cut off from all who loved me.
And so. you think by going
after Vhagar. you will...
what?
If I kill her.
I will have paid
some of my debt to Rhaenyra.
I would at least have grounds
to sue for her mercy.
- You will more likely die.
- Then I will have paid all of it.
I will die absolved
if I cannot live that way.
[Sheepstealer roars]
Let me help you. then.
You cannot battle Vhagar alone.
But the two of us
may yet prevail.
Why would you do
such a thing?
I had no dragon either
when I was young.
Did you know that?
My mother died in childbed
when I was three years of age.
My brother sank into sadness.
I was alone.
just as you have been.
I should have done better.
Rhaena.
[Caraxes whistling]
- You lie.
- I did not summon them.
- You'd betray your own daughter?
- I have not. I swear it.
She does not yet know
who you are.
[bellowing]
[Daemon] Leave him.
They will tear you
from the sky.
[whimpering]
Run! Run!
[dragon roaring]
[dragons bellowing]
Go!
[dragons vocalizing]
[speaking High Valyrian]
- Call off your dragon!
- What is your agreement
with Sheepstealer's rider?
Answer carefully.
You will not have
another chance to deceive me.
I never wished to deceive you.
- Then. speak!
- Call off your dragon.
[dragons bellowing]
[grunting]
[Rhaena shouting]
Please. Rhaenyra.
She's not herself.
- [Rhaena shouting]
- [dragons vocalizing]
Rhaena?
It wasn't you.
She was Sheepstealer's rider?
All this time. you knew.
This is finished!
[dragons roaring]
Move!
[roaring continues]
[shouting in High Valyrian]
[screeching]
- Your Grace!
- Help Daemon! Go!
Go!
[dragons continue roaring]
[Rhaenyra shouting]
[gasping]
With me!
[screeching]
No!
[screeching continues]
Escort the queen.
I will finish this.
[screeching]
[grunting]
[Yelping. screeching]
[whimpers]
[Mysaria]
It is magnificent in its way.
[Madam Sylvi] I saw it once before when
I petitioned the queen.
Do you know
what it brings to my mind?
A hundred sharp little cocks
all vying for attention.
The queen wishes
at the moment
to hear no more petitions.
That is a mistake.
I agree.
There is villainy and violence
on her streets now.
The people are afraid
to go out by night.
It is to her detriment only.
Those who look
to her for relief
now feel she's turned
her back on them.
I wished to hear from you
how you fare in this city.
And if there are others
who may find it a consolation
to come to me
with their troubles
and have them considered.
You make yourself her proxy.
Someone must.
Do you not agree?
If she herself is reluctant.
I can perhaps then bring
certain dilemmas before her
when I judge her mood
to be more accommodating.
You are changed.
This... has changed you.
My heart is with the downtrodden
as it has ever been.
Is it?
Or have you styled yourself
a champion
in order to access these halls?
Look at you.
Standing at the foot
of the throne
wearing a silk worth a year
of my earnings.
promising to whisper
into the ear of a queen.
You thrill now to a tune
you once abhorred.
Does it not occur to you
that from this position
I may help those
who have no avenue?
What power
do you have in truth?
Except to flatter and cajole?
Ah.
Is that why
you called me here?
To look on the trappings so that
someone would hold you in awe?
This was a mistake.
How common
I must seem to you.
That will be all.
Some advice. my lady.
These people
are not your own.
You would do well
to remember that.
Within the walls
of the highborn.
a whore will always and ever
remain a whore.
[footsteps receding]
[dragons bellowing]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[bellowing continues]
Find her a room.
I do not wish to see her.
[Alicent] Aemond?
Mother.
Your friend Alys.
- She's not my friend.
- Oh.
She doesn't want me
to stay here.
If I'm disturbing
some understanding between...
No.
- I should perhaps not have come.
- No.
I will... I will take my leave.
if that would behoove you.
I'm glad you came.
I brought you something.
[cup scraping]
Spiced wine.
I remember a time when you would
not fall asleep without it.
Alys doesn't trust you.
Who do you trust?
I...
I tried to kill Aegon.
I know.
[whispering]
My dear...
foolish boy.
Your Grace.
[door opens]
- [door closes]
- No. stay.
She implored me
not to tell you.
She could not face you.
I wished only to protect her.
From what?
What do you think I am?
Y-You are my wife.
She's my daughter.
One I-I-I have long neglected.
Was she not seeking. in all this.
my favor or yours?
I have looked a hundred times
at that skull you brought...
thinking it was the villain
who killed my son.
I am sorry.
but you must see now that
I kept no scheme against you.
I did only what I thought
was best. Rhaenyra.
Please.
It's late.
[door opens. closes]
[♪ somber music playing]
[whispering] I am sorry.
To Jace.
To you.
You would have been queen.
[Baela] Enough.
[♪ somber music
continues playing]
You will begin anew.
[Alyn] More Hightower loyalists were found.
Alert the confessors.
[guard] Ser Alyn.
It was left for you.
[breathing shakily]
[owl screeching]
[bird squawking]
[thud]
Alys.
Idiot.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[screaming]
[baby crying]
[baby continues crying]
[whimpers]
[gasps]
[Dreamfyre chirping]
[snarling and screeching]
Dracarys!
[chickens clucking]
[♪ gentle music playing]
[wind whistling]
[distorted noises intensifying]
[fire crackling softly]
[♪ soft. dramatic music playing]
[bones rattling]
[Rhaenyra] It was Rhaena
he was hiding all along.
He lied.
I did not lead you astray.
And yet you cannot say
he betrayed me
so much as he would not
betray his daughter.
This time.
But does it not prove
he is willing to deceive you
- if he judges it necessary?
- [scoffs]
And you've never done the same?
I've acted only
in your interests.
You have sought
to turn me from him.
Pouring your honey in my ear.
whispering. encouraging.
seeking to make me
in your image.
In my image?
Your Grace. have I ever
counseled you to do aught
but what Viserys
would have you do in his place?
As you have ofttimes said.
is your own desire.
Yes. and in hewing to his vision.
what have I reaped?
Peace?
Prosperity?
Ah. the gratitude
of my subjects.
My father was not a dreamer.
But his whole life
was a dream.
Do not lose faith.
You are on the precipice
of a great victory.
The uncertainties
that oppress you
will soon be resolved.
Those who oppose you
will fall away.
Even Aemond
is all but vanquished.
You will be queen
for many years after this.
And your children's children
after you.
Just a little longer.
Do you think...
I am worthy?
In this moment. my queen.
Rhaenyra.
I have never been
more certain of it.
[♪ soft. dramatic music playing]
[faint rhythmic beating]
[faint beating continues]
[beating grows louder]
A final stand then.
Ser Tyland.
Your Grace.
We claim this land for Rhaenyra.
Queen of the Seven Kingdoms.
You will throw down your arms
and make ready
to swear your fealty.
[softly]
Oh. no. no. no. no. no.
[Tyland] Your Grace?
Will you flee after all?
We shall not surrender
to the false queen.
[laughter]
Is that you.
Tyland Lannister?
Your queen's been
looking for you.
Tell us where the gold is.
and you will die
with your ears still attached.
Behold me now!
[horse whinnying]
I am Aegon Targaryen!
- Viserys' true heir!
- [distant bellowing]
The sixth King of the Andals
and the Rhoynar
and the First Men!
I was anointed
by the High Septon
in the light of the Seven.
And it is in their light
that I stand before you now!
Strike me down!
And the Stranger
will take retribution.
The Warrior's sword
will be judgment upon you.
[dragon snarling]
[chuckles] Yes.
Yes. cowards.
- You might well retreat.
- [rumbling]
For now you see me
as I truly am!
- [dragon snarling]
- [gasping softly]
Dreadful in vengeance!
- Righteous and glorious!
- [horses whinnying]
[dragon bellowing
and growling]
[dragon chirping]
[whispering] Sunfyre.
[Sunfyre chittering]
Sunfyre.
Dracarys.
Run! Save yourselves!
[soldiers screaming]
[Aegon yelling]
[screaming continues]
[Aegon continues yelling]
[Aegon laughing]
[bellowing]
Oh.
Decent ale. that.
I thought you might enjoy it.
- [gulping] Mm.
- I have had word...
since we last spoke
of a most distressing incident.
My whisperers tell me that
Daemon Targaryen struck you.
In the street.
In front of all the commoners
passing by.
An intolerable insult
to someone of your stature.
But then. uh. it's almost to be
expected from those people.
She did tell me
not to go into town.
- To be fair.
- Ludicrous.
A man needs his sustenance
and cheer.
But it is obvious
Rhaenyra and her ilk
regard you only as a tool.
To be used and reprimanded.
Whereas I understand...
who you really are.
You said last time...
that you could give me
a lordship.
And a castle.
Honeyholt.
Honeyholt?
[chuckles]
Honeyholt is a trifle.
It seems that
Driftmark itself
may soon be without a master.
Lord of the Tides.
What do you think of that?
- [chuckles]
- [mugs clanking]
They will laugh
at you no more...
when they see you as you are.
No.
They will burn.
♪